bzoink.com 2006-12-05

# Bzoink - Privacy Policy

## The Short Version

  * We never sell, or share, your personal information.
  * Nothing is displayed unless you want it to be.
  * Want out? You can delete your account at any time. Free and fast.
  * We protect you as though you were us.

## What information is collected?

The only pieces of required information that we collect directly from you are birthdate and email address.

We are prohibited by law, according to the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998](http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm "Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998") (COPPA), to collect personal information from individuals age 12 years and under without parental consent. Therefore, we collect your birthdate at registration to confirm that you are of legal age to use the site, and to prove that you said you were of a certain age should any legalities arise.

We collect your email address to restrict any one person from creating dozens of accounts on the site, and to send you notification and update emails if you have selected to receive such mailings.

We do sometimes log your IP address as well as the date and time of access. This is to prevent abuse of the service and allows us to ban certain individuals from the site. Logging such information also assists in any police or higher authority cases that sometimes are brought to the internet.

Any other information we collect will be provided directly by you. Information includes, but is not limited to, such things as profiles, quizlets, polls, and surveys. All of the information collected from these areas of the site are optional and ONLY put them out there if you don't mind people knowing it. This is the internet, use discretion.

## Cookies and Tracking

We sometimes place cookies on your computer. The main purpose for this is if you choose the 'Remember me next time!' option while logging in. Without placing a cookie on your computer we'd have no way of knowing who you are and you would be required to login every time you come back. We also place various temporary cookies on your computer, that expire when you leave the site, while you're here to keep track of which surveys, quizlets, polls, or other areas of the site you've accessed so that our 'served' numbers aren't inaccurate. We want to count one person taking the same survey 57 times as only one.

## Advertising

We currently outsource our advertising solutions to other companies. That means that the ads you see are not directly handled by us personally. The companies that we choose to serve ads may place their own cookies on your computer so they don't show you the same ad twice. These companies should be considered separate entities and not directly linked to Bzoink. Furthermore, any such companies are not covered by this privacy policy.

## Is my personal information safe here?

On our end, your personal data is stored on private servers that serve only our web sites. This means no one else has a web site on our servers, and also that only we have access. There's another plus here too, Bzoink is currently a one man operation. There's no way for an unhappy employee to get in contact with your information. One person controls it all, and it's not getting out because of an in-house dispute. Simply doesn't happen.

## Privacy Policy changes

Of course, our privacy policy is subject to change at any time. Usually just adding something in to your benefit, or adding issues related to a new feature. Please know that we will always be looking out for your best interest and privacy.

Last modified: August 18, 2005
